<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Catchme</string>
    
    <string name="text_welcome_title">Welcome to "The Love Quest"</string>
    <string name="text_welcome">
        Dear Aindrea, \n
        \n
        Today is your lucky day: you\'re going to experience a lovely trip around Verona prepared by your boyfriend Mattia, in the quest of Love.\n
        \n
        This application especially made for this purpose will guide through this adventure. We don\'t want to tell you much yet to not spoil the fun. 
        All that we can say is that your will be required to walk around quite a bit. \n
        \n
        So, let\'s get started! Please press the \"Continue\" button below
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_instructions_title">A few instructions</string>
    <string name="text_instructions">
        There aren\'t many rules for today, but just to make sure you know what to do: here are a few instructions to successfully complete The Love Quest\n
        \n
        - this application is going to guide you through a list of steps \n\n
        - every time you complete a step, press \"Continue\" to go to the next one \n\n
        - some steps are going to involve you walking somewhere. When you reach your target, please take a picture of yourself in that place to prove you\'ve been there before continuing on to the step after \n\n
        - after some steps we\'ll ask you to text Mattia to provide him your position (don\'t worry, we\'ll remind you when you need to do so)\n\n
        - if you ever want to go previous steps, simply use the \"back\" button of your phone. Indeed, why don\'t you try it right now? Go back to the welcome screen and then \"Continue\" again to come back here \n\n
        - when you need to leave the application (to send a text, make a call, etc.), just open it up again and it should resume from where you left it. You will find it in your application list under \"Catchme\". \n\n
        - if the application doesn\'t resume properly, but instead starts from the beginning, just quickly skip the steps that you have already completed \n\n
        - please leave your internet connection on in order for all the steps to work properly \n\n
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_getReady_title">Let\'s get ready!</string>
    <string name="text_getReady">
        Ok, it\'s time to get ready now and start this adventure! Have a shower, wear something, put your make-up on, etc. etc. \n
        \n
        When you\'re ready to go grab your phone and \"Continue\" to start your Love Quest!
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_firstText_title">First Text</string>
    <string name="text_firstText">
        Time to text Mattia: \"ON MY WAY\" 
	</string>
    
    <string name="map_sacher_title">Target 1: Sacher</string>
    <string name="map_sacher">Gelateria \"Il Gelatone\"</string>

    <string name="text_sacherReached_title">Target 1: Sacher - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_sacherReached">
        Wow, you reached the first target, congratulations! Woo hoo!\n\n
        Awww, do you remember all the times we had sacher here? Mmmh, that\'s soooo good. How lovely are our strolls in the summer nights! 
        I just love to walk around with you, chat, have an ice cream and relax. I can\'t wait for the weather to get warmer and start againg.\n
        \n
        \n
        Ok, since you reached your first target, don\'t forget to take a picture to prove you\'ve been here! Exit the application (just use the \"home\" button of your phone), 
        take a picture, and then open it up again to continue.
    </string>
    <string name="text_sacherReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_sacherReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"SACHER REACHED\" </string>
        
    <string name="map_pizzeria70_title">Second Target: Pizzeria 70</string>
    <string name="map_pizzeria70">Mmmh, mediterranea...</string>
    
    <string name="map_viaBadile_title">Via Badile 45</string>
    <string name="map_viaBadile">Old house</string>
    
    <string name="map_firstPizza_title">First pizza</string>
    <string name="map_firstPizza">Piazza bra\'</string>
    
    <string name="map_viaStella_title">Taverna di Via Stella</string>
    <string name="map_viaStella">polenta?</string>
    
    <string name="map_pozzoAmore_title">Pozzo dell\'Amore</string>
    <string name="map_pozzoAmore"></string>
    
    <string name="map_ferraris_title">Ferraris</string>
    <string name="map_ferraris">Museo della radio</string>
    
    <string name="map_oldHouse_title">Antonia\'s house</string>
    <string name="map_oldHouse"></string>
    
    <string name="map_pontePietra_title">Ponte Pietra</string>
    <string name="map_pontePietra"></string>
    
    <string name="map_torreLamberti_title">Torre dei Lamberti</string>
    <string name="map_torreLamberti"></string>
    
    <string name="map_home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="map_home">come back!</string>
    

</resources>