<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Catchme</string>
    
    <string name="text_welcome_title">Welcome to "The Love Quest"</string>
    <string name="text_welcome">
        Dear Aindrea, \n
        \n
        Today is your lucky day: you\'re going to experience a lovely trip around Verona prepared by your boyfriend Mattia, in the quest of Love.\n
        \n
        This application especially made for this purpose will guide through this adventure. We don\'t want to tell you much yet to not spoil the fun. 
        All that we can say is that your will be required to walk around quite a bit. \n
        \n
        So, let\'s get started! Please press the \"Continue\" button below
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_instructions_title">A few instructions</string>
    <string name="text_instructions">
        There aren\'t many rules for today, but just to make sure you know what to do: here are a few instructions to successfully complete The Love Quest\n
        \n
        - this application is going to guide you through a list of steps \n\n
        - every time you complete a step, press \"Continue\" to go to the next one \n\n
        - some steps are going to involve you walking somewhere. When you reach your target, please take a picture of yourself in that place to prove you\'ve been there before continuing on to the step after \n\n
        - after some steps we\'ll ask you to text Mattia to provide him your position (don\'t worry, we\'ll remind you when you need to do so)\n\n
        - if you don\'t feel like walking and prefer to use the bus, you can; just know that all the targets are at walking distance from each other, so we suggest you to take your time and use your feet to enjoy it more :-)
        - there is no rush! enjoy this adventure
        - if you ever want to go previous steps, simply use the \"back\" button of your phone. Indeed, why don\'t you try it right now? Go back to the welcome screen and then \"Continue\" again to come back here \n\n
        - when you need to leave the application (to send a text, make a call, etc.), just open it up again and it should resume from where you left it. You will find it in your application list under \"Catchme\". \n\n
        - if the application doesn\'t resume properly, but instead starts from the beginning, just quickly skip the steps that you have already completed \n\n
        - please leave your internet connection on in order for all the steps to work properly \n\n
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_getReady_title">Let\'s get ready!</string>
    <string name="text_getReady">
        Ok, it\'s time to get ready now and start this adventure! Have a shower, wear something, put your make-up on, etc. etc. \n
        \n
        When you\'re ready to go grab your phone and \"Continue\" to start your Love Quest!
	</string>
	
    <string name="text_firstText_title">First Text</string>
    <string name="text_firstText">
        Time to text Mattia: \"ON MY WAY\" 
	</string>
    
    <string name="map_sacher_title">Target 1: Sacher</string>
    <string name="map_sacher">Gelateria \"Il Gelatone\"</string>
    <string name="text_sacherReached_title">Target 1: Sacher - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_sacherReached">
        Wow, you reached the first target, congratulations! Woo hoo!\n\n
        Awww, do you remember all the times we had sacher here? Mmmh, that\'s soooo good. How lovely are our strolls in the summer nights! 
        I just love to walk around with you, chat, have an ice cream and relax. I can\'t wait for the weather to get warmer and start againg.\n
        \n
        \n
        Ok, since you reached your first target, don\'t forget to take a picture to prove you\'ve been here! Exit the application (just use the \"home\" button of your phone), 
        take a picture, and then open it up again to continue.
    </string>
    <string name="text_sacherReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_sacherReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"SACHER REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_pizzeria70_title">Target 2: Pizzeria 70</string>
    <string name="map_pizzeria70">Mmmh, mediterranea...</string>
	<string name="text_pizzeria70Reached_title">Target 2: Pizzeria 70 - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_pizzeria70Reached">
        We love our pizzas here, don\'t we? But what I most love is to have pizza with you: spend the night chatting, hearing your stories, and laughing. Mmmh, shall we have a pizza tonight? :-)
    </string>
    <string name="text_pizzeria70ReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_pizzeria70ReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"PIZZERIA 70 REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_viaBadile_title">Target 3: Via Badile</string>
    <string name="map_viaBadile">Old Via Badile\'s house</string>
    <string name="text_viaBadileReached_title">Target 3: Via Badile - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_viaBadileReached">
        Your old via badile house. So many things happened here! Do you remember the little \"ou\" man drawn on the whiteboard? And that time when they cut your electricity? 
        And when I did the shopping for you? And when I showed you how to cook carbonara? And the first Valentine\'s Day? And...oh, I better stop and let you continue your journey :) 
        remember to take a picture!
    </string>
    <string name="text_viaBadileReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_viaBadileReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"VIA BADILE REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_ferraris_title">Target 4: Ferraris</string>
    <string name="map_ferraris">where we first met</string>
    <string name="text_ferrarisReached_title">Target 4: Ferraris - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_ferrarisReached">
        I will never forget the first time I saw you. I was doing my museum walk, going around the room and pretending to be interested in those old radios, when I saw you standing in a corner, 
        looking at some electonic stuff. You were wearing your black short jacket, and brown trousers. I remember I thought \"wow, she\'s so beautiful! I wander who she is. Maybe Antonia knows her 
        and can introduce me to her\". And then we went to that bar with crappy karaoke, I had an hot chocolate and you had a coke. But really you wanted an hot chocolate too :-) 
        Then we exchanged numbers, Andreas. Then there was the Tibet night. And the rest is history...
    </string>
    <string name="text_ferrarisReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_ferrarisReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"FERRARIS REACHED\" </string>

    <string name="map_firstPizza_title">Target 5: First Date</string>
    <string name="map_firstPizza">Piazza bra\', first pizza place</string>
    <string name="text_firstPizzaReached_title">Target 5: First Date - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_firstPizzaReached">
        Here we had our first date, do you remember? I\'m sure you do. Oh, I was so nervous! While I was waiting for you outside the school I had butterflies in my stomach. \n
        I had margherita and you had prosciutto e funghi...aww, such a polite couple! Eh eh. You told me about your experiences around the world, your family, your cat, etc. etc. 
        I couldn\'t stop listening to you, I was already in love :-) ah ah, and then you were too shy to give me a small kiss to thank me for paying for the pizza. Awww, bless you.\n
        And then we walked, and walked, and walked...there was always an extra ultimo giro just to chat some more.
    </string>
    <string name="text_firstPizzaReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_firstPizzaReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"FIRST DATE REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_oldHouse_title">Target 6: Antonia\'s house</string>
    <string name="map_oldHouse"></string>
    <string name="text_oldHouseReached_title">Target 6: Antonia\'s house - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_oldHouseReached">
        I used to take you back here after our walks, do you remember? And then we would exchange a little kiss on the cheek, eh eh. Buonanotte, mwah mwah.
        And immediatly after we would both think \"oh, i should have kissed her!\". Ah, good memories. \n
        We have so many memories here! She was definitely crazy, but thank God she was there and we met. Oh, do you remember that time when I slept here? 
        Ah ah, and then I had to sneak out in the morning. Fun :-)
    </string>
    <string name="text_oldHouseReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_oldHouseReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"ANTONIA\'S HOUSE REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_cinemaFiume_title">Target 7: Cinema Fiume</string>
    <string name="map_cinemaFiume"></string>
    <string name="text_cinemaFiumeReached_title">Target 7: Cinema Fiume - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_cinemaFiumeReached">
        \"You\'re very nice tonight\" \"Uh uh, thank you\". Oh, I\'ll never forget that moment! It was our second date, we came here to watch Enchanted.
        I wanted to hold your hand during the film, but I was too shy. You were wearing a pink top and a scarf, and you told me how much you loved scarfs. 
        By the way, that\'s why I bought you that scarf for christmas (that one that you\'ve never wore!)
    </string>
    <string name="text_cinemaFiumeReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_cinemaFiumeReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"FIUME REACHED\" </string>
    
    <!-- TODO add CastelVecchio here -->
    
    <string name="map_pozzoAmore_title">Target 8: Pozzo dell\'Amore</string>
    <string name="map_pozzoAmore"></string>
    <string name="text_pozzoAmoreReached_title">Target 8: Pozzo dell\'Amore - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_pozzoAmoreReached">
        Ok, this is difficult. You might not remember this, but I do. It was our first date and we were walking around the center, whilst I was explaining everything to you
        about Verona, ancient roman, etc. We arrived here - not exactly here, but near here - and there was a bombolone sleeping at the side of the road. 
        You were walking on that side, so I exchanged place with you and protected you while walking near him. 
        And from that moment on I protected my piccolina from everything bad around her.
    </string>
    <string name="text_pozzoAmoreReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_pozzoAmoreReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"POZZO AMORE REACHED\" </string>

    <string name="map_viaStella_title">Target 9: Taverna di Via Stella</string>
    <string name="map_viaStella">polenta?</string>
    <string name="text_viaStellaReached_title">Target 9: Taverna di Via Stella - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_viaStellaReached">
		Of all the times we\'ve been here, I particularly remember when I first met your parents. Oh, I was really nervous! It was just a couple of months after 
		we got togheter. First we met in piazza bra\' and then we came here, and we had a lovely evening. I think your mum started loving me from that night :-)\n
		I was nervous but not scared: I knew already I would have been with you for a looooooong time...
    </string>
    <string name="text_viaStellaReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_viaStellaReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"VIA STELLA REACHED\" </string>

    <string name="map_pontePietra_title">Target 10: Ponte Pietra</string>
    <string name="map_pontePietra"></string>
    <string name="text_pontePietraReached_title">Target 10: Ponte Pietra - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_pontePietraReached">
        Here is where we exchanged our first kiss...oh no, wait, we didn\'t! Eh eh. You were too shy, but nevermind. It all fell into place in the end. \n
        I remember when that night when I was walking home you texted me \"thank you for being so patient, sorry if I\'m so shy\" and I replied 
        \"don\'t worry, it will all come at the right time\". Indeed, the right time arrived short after.
    </string>
    <string name="text_pontePietraReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_pontePietraReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"PONTE PIETRA REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="map_torreLamberti_title">Target 11: Torre dei Lamberti</string>
    <string name="map_torreLamberti"></string>
    <string name="text_torreLambertiReached_title">Target 11: Torre dei Lamberti - Reached!</string>
    <string name="text_torreLambertiReached">
        You knew you would have arrived here sooner or later. This is where our love started: the first kiss. I remember every second of that day.\n
        First I came to take you at Antonia\'s house, and we walked to the center holding hands for the first time. Actually my hand hurted yours accidentally, 
        but you said \"uh, holding hands, nice\" so we did...but hey, nevermind, that was cool :-) then we walked and I brought you here, at the Torre dei Lamberti,
        right at the top; I showed you where I lived, and that was the moment when you realized I didn\'t live near San Zeno. You understood I really cared about you,
        I was willing to walk all that way just for you, so you hugged me. And that was the moment I kissed you, just before telling you how beautiful you are 
        and how much I liked you. That\'s when our story began.\n
        \n
        P.S. You better take a nice picture here :-)
    </string>
    <string name="text_torreLambertiReachedText_title">Text time</string>
    <string name="text_torreLambertiReachedText">Time to text Mattia: \"TORRE DEI LAMBERTI REACHED\" </string>
    
    <string name="text_timeToGoHome_title">Time to go home</string>
    <string name="text_timeToGoHome">
        Congratulations, your quest is complete! You have been really good, you got here. Weeeeee...oh no, hang on a second, it\' not over yet!
        There is still one last target to reach: home. \n
        \n
        Get home to complete your quest and find love
    </string>
    
    <string name="map_home_title">Target 12: Home</string>
    <string name="map_home">come back!</string>

</resources>